Please Rotate Your Device 90

For the best experience, turn your mobile device portrait mode.

Do Not Sell or Share/Process My Personal Information for Targeted Advertising
=============================================================================

Last Updated: June 4, 2024

* English
* Español (Americas)

English

Your Privacy Choices: Opt-out of sale of personal information and Opt-out of sharing or processing personal information for targeted ads.
=========================================================================================================================================

NBCUniversal offers our customers certain choices about how we use their information. Applicable law gives residents of California, Connecticut, Colorado, Utah or Virginia the right to opt-out of the “sale” of their personal information or the sharing/processing your personal information for targeted advertising.  

**Targeted Advertising Opt-Outs**

Certain NBCUniversal brands feature targeted advertising. Advertising, including targeted-based advertising, enables these NBCUniversal brands to provide you certain content for free or at a low cost and offers that are more relevant to you. To provide this advertising on NBCUniversal Services and on other online services, NBCUniversal allows third parties to receive certain information to add to a profile about your device, browser, or you.

Certain laws broadly define “sale” of personal information in a way that may include allowing third parties to receive some information to add to a profile about your device, browser, or you. In addition, this activity may be defined by law to be sharing or processing personal information for targeted advertising. Residents of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, and Virginia may opt out of certain of these activities.

On some of our websites and applications when you click the “Your Privacy Choices” link in the website footer or in the application settings menu, you will be shown a Consent Management Platform (CMP), this tool allows you to opt out of the “sale” of your personal information or sharing or processing it for targeted advertising purposes. Please note, if you use different NBCUniversal sites/apps on different browsers/devices you will need to opt out on each site/app and browser/device where you want your choice to apply.  In some cases, you may also be presented with form fields to complete, in those cases we ask for your email address or other information so we may add it to an appropriate suppression list.

In other cases, you will be directed to this page where we provide additional information and options for you to learn more about your choices and how to opt out from targeted advertising more broadly.

If you are a resident of California, Connecticut, Colorado, Utah or Virginia, to opt out of us selling or sharing/processing your personal information such as your name, email address and other associated personal information for targeted advertising activities as described above, please fill out this [online form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/17e5cb00-ad90-47f5-a58d-77597d9d2c16/cda09e33-f935-4960-87de-afa722cef3c2).

If you opt out, you will still see ads but they may be less relevant or, depending on your choice, based only on our first-party information about you.

**Additional Targeted Advertising Opt-Out Tools**

In addition to the opt out tools, above, there are third party tools you may use with respect to targeted advertising.  
The Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) provides you with a choice as to whether participating third parties can use your information to provide targeted  advertising. To opt out of sharing your information with such participating third parties for targeted advertising, please use the following tools:

* For websites: the **DAA WebChoices Tool**, available at [http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN](https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN).
* For mobile applications and connected devices, such as smart TVs or streaming devices, you should review the device’s settings and select the option that allows you to disable automatic content recognition or ad tracking.  Typically, to opt out, such devices require you to select options like “limit ad tracking” or to disable options such as “interest-based advertising,” “interactive TV,” or “smart interactivity”.  These settings vary by device type.

When enabling advertising opt-out tools please understand the following:

* The opt-outs described above are device and browser based. Because the information being shared relates to your device ID and/or browser ID, you will need to opt out on each device and each browser.
* Opt-outs may be stored via cookies. If you clear cookies or if your browser blocks cookies, your opt-out cookie may no longer be available. In this case your opt-out choices can not to be honored.

We do not maintain or control these opt-out mechanisms and are not responsible for their operation. NBCUniversal may still use your data to deliver contextual advertising, conduct cross-device tracking to serve you first-party ads directly, or for nontargeted advertising purposes, such as attribution and analytics.

**Opt-Out Tools for Sensitive Personal Information**

Where you have opted in on a mobile device to provide specific geolocation, you can change your permissions in your device settings.

Footer menu [AD CHOICES](https://www.nbcuniversal.com/privacy/cookies#accordionheader2) [Privacy Policy](https://www.nbcuniversal.com/privacy "Privacy") [YOUR PRIVACY CHOICES](https://www.nbcuniversal.com/privacy/notrtoo) [CA Notice](https://www.nbcuniversal.com/privacy/california-consumer-privacy-act) [Terms Of Service (Updated July 7, 2023)](https://www.nbcuniversal.com/terms "Terms Of Service")

Secondary Footer [Supply Chain Values](https://www.cmcsa.com/esg-reporting "Supply Chain Values") [Advertise With Us](https://together.nbcuni.com/advertise/?utm_source=nbcuniversal&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=property_ad_pages)

© 2024 NBCUNIVERSAL MEDIA, LLC.
